{
    "subject": "resource/Rudyard_Kipling",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Bombay_Presidency",
    "human_readable": "Rudyard Kipling was born in Bombay Presidency.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8419604897499084,
            "question": "Name the city where Rudyard Kipling was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8317516446113586,
            "question": "Where was Rudyard Kipling born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7718725800514221,
            "question": "When was Rudyard Kipling born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6651248931884766,
            "question": "What is the name of the region where Rudyard Kipling was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5289574861526489,
            "question": "Was Rudyard Kipling born in a British colony?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5219936966896057,
            "question": "In which country was Bombay Presidency located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4176270067691803,
            "question": "What is Rudyard Kipling known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23638026416301727,
            "question": "What are some famous works by Rudyard Kipling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13869787752628326,
            "question": "Did Rudyard Kipling write any stories about India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10295819491147995,
            "question": "What type of literature is Rudyard Kipling most famous for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rudyard Kipling was born in Bombay Presidency.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6765_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Rudyard Kipling write any stories about India?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6765_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some famous works by Rudyard Kipling?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6765_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Rudyard Kipling known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6765_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6765_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6765_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6765_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6765_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6765_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6765_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6765_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6765_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6765_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6765_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, Rudyard Kipling was indeed born in Bombay Presidency, British India. This information is mentioned in multiple documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6765/re-ranker-msmarco/78.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6765/re-ranker-msmarco/62.txt, and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6765/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Rudyard Kipling's birthplace, which is stated to be in the Bombay Presidency of British India. Therefore, the statement \"Rudyard Kipling was born in Bombay Presidency\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}